English
英语
And uh
嗯
Sorry
对不起的
And uh
嗯
Don't say smith
别说史密斯
Sorry
对不起的
So
所以
Oh
哦
Sorry
对不起的
Mhm
MHM
Thank you
谢谢
Me too
我也是
Want
想要
Where are you
你在哪里
Mhm
MHM
What's your name
你叫什么名字
No
不
Who
谁
Uh yesterday come on
呃昨天来吧
Apple
苹果
Good
好
Don't change the subject
别改变话题
What for
为什么
This year
今年
Good
好
What's this for
你这是做什么用的
What?
什么？
Fine
法恩
Breakfast sunday masses quantity
周日早餐，大众数量
Suggest
建议
Hello
你好
Good morning
早上好
Oh
哦
Thank you so easy
太感谢你了
Oh
哦
Come on
快点
Sorry
对不起的
And uh
嗯
Good morning
早上好
Good
好
What
什么
To
到
That
那
The spring
春天
Good evening
晚上好
Stream
河流
Excuse me
不好意思
All right
好吧，
Wake up
醒来
Go for it
去吧，去吧
So many people
有那么多人
Turns out this is my roommate boy
原来这是我室友的儿子
You can find happiness in you
你能在自己身上找到幸福
Yeah
是啊
Please no
拜托，不要
Excuse me
不好意思
Some
一些
Oh
哦
Something
一些东西
Once
一次
Say nothing
什么都别说
How are you
你好吗？
Come on
快点
Okay
可以
No
不
Truck
卡车
It's all because of you
全是因为你
What science project
什么科学项目
Of course, this is short
当然，这很短
Your name is
你的名字是
What's the defense council
什么是国防委员会
Wind
风
Tom what you said
汤姆，你说什么
What
什么
That does not seem so daunting
看上去并不可怕
Discovery
发现
Indirect
间接
Maybe we thought we were spending time with the food. Instead we're stuck on the side
或许我们以为我们在食物上花时间。相反，我们被挡在了一边
三十九
Then
然后
Oh my god
哦天啊
When uh
当UH
After I take my money out of the window
在我把钱从窗户拿出来之后
Thank you
谢谢
Oh i'm sorry
哦，对不起
Sure
当然
Right?
对吗？
Guys
伙计们
We just need to find the safest possible place. And wait
我们只需要找到最安全的地方。等等
Where
在哪里？
Me
我
What's your name
你叫什么名字
Thank you
谢谢
Um
嗯
Here's
这里是
An honest mistake, because crazy
一个诚实的错误，因为疯狂
Okay, so my mom and dad
好吧，那我爸妈
Another exit
另一个出口
And uh
嗯
Thank you
谢谢
Oh my god
哦天啊
Study
书房
Sister
姊妹
And for me
对我来说
Mhm
MHM
Wow
哇哦
Stop
停止
Um
嗯
I want to find out
我想知道
Are you suffering from?
你在受苦吗？
Oh
哦
Morning
早晨
La
洛杉矶
Sustained
持续
Only six seven. And the worst thing
只有67个。最糟糕的是
The
这个
What's the point
有什么意义
Okay thank you
好的，谢谢
How do you do
你好啊
Are you
你是吗
Hello
你好
I will
我会的
Thanks
谢谢
Yeah
是啊
Of course
当然
Yeah
是啊
A whiskey definition
威士忌酒的定义
Two
二
Thank you
谢谢
Oh
哦
Sure
当然
Thanks
谢谢
Now
现在
Pronounce it direct sun back
把它说成太阳直射回来
Let's go
我们走吧
Sure
当然
Mhm
MHM
What
什么
Who
谁
Fine
法恩
Excuse my english isn't
抱歉，我的英语不好
Oh sir
哦，先生
All right
好吧，
Good morning
早上好
Sorry
对不起的
Oh my god
哦天啊
I highly doubt it
我非常怀疑
There is only one of you
你们中只有一个人
Super
超级的
Never had a wonderful story
从来没有一个精彩的故事
Hello
你好
Baby sister matches
小妹妹匹配
A single man
单身男子
So how different are we talking here
所以我们在这里谈的有多不同
I'm sorry
我很抱歉
Hello
你好
Production
生产
Did you know
你知道吗
We have
我们有
Thanks
谢谢
Whatever
管他呢
What
什么
Somebody missed our last meeting today
有人错过了我们今天的最后一次会议
20 health benefits
20个健康福利
Thank you
谢谢
Wedding reception is very bad
婚宴很糟糕
Hello
你好
Sure english
当然英语
There is no greater gift than mine
再没有比我更伟大的礼物了
In fact
事实上
Yeah
是啊
Hey dad um
嘿爸爸呃
Yeah, I guess on began a moment
是啊，我想开始的时候
I have no
我没有
And
和
High school
高中
Right
对吗？
Oh no
哦不
Thanks
谢谢
Bye bye
再见
Doing some
做一些
Nice to meet you
很高兴见到你
Hey
嘿
Baby
婴儿
About it now
关于它现在
Yes
是的
One of your closest friends woke up this morning
你最亲密的朋友今早醒来
Not happen
不会发生
You wished for you
你希望你
Hi
您好!
It's houses famous. Okay, listen to me on this side
很有名的房子。好吧，听我说这边
Hi
您好!
Tree
树
This boy
这个男孩
I can make something came up with what?
我能想出什么办法？
I'm
我是
I'm sorry, street and was surprised
抱歉，街上的人都很惊讶
You know my brother
你知道我哥哥
Anyhow
总之
So
所以
Hello
你好
English
英语
Good
好
Give me one thing
给我一件事
Thank you
谢谢
How lovely to meet you
很高兴认识你
Noise
噪声
Can you help me
你能帮我吗
What happened?
怎么了？
OK
好啊
Safety first structure
安全第一结构
Stress
强调
Um
嗯
Yeah
是啊
Are you then
你就是那个
Phone call
打个电话
Then on
然后在
Come on
快点
How interesting
多有趣啊
No it isn't
不，不是的
So simple
太简单了
Thank you
谢谢
Ok, city school student first place
好吧，城市学校的学生第一名
Your brain science people, right? So you figure it out
你的脑科学专家，对吧？ 所以你想出来了
U s method, the door with such
我们的方法，门是这样的
Do me a favor. Interference from, okay
帮我个忙。干扰，好的
This is going to be a traumatic situation
这将会是一个痛苦的局面
We have evidence on three
我们有三人的证据
And what you're saying is true, there is no way to keep a record of our progress and not
你说的是真的，没有办法记录下我们的进展
Oh um
哦，嗯
Doesn't well
不是很好
Yes
是的
No way! For structural problems
不行！ 因为结构上的问题
Wait
等待
Screwed
拧紧
But you said everything was set, but your memory, right
但你说一切都安排好了，但是你的记忆，对吧
Thank you
谢谢
In my eyes
在我眼里
That's dreams no no
那是梦不不不
I mean, you do realize there is a killer for me right now and I'm going to die over and over again until you get a bigger room
我是说，你知道现在有个杀手要杀我我要一遍又一遍地死去直到你有个更大的房间
Understood just so so
我是这么理解的
Colleges
大学
I'm very
我非常.
And you're gonna say that
你就这么说吧
Mhm
MHM
Yeah
是啊
Mhm
MHM
Hello
你好
No
不
Who are you
你是谁
Banana
香蕉
A really gentlemen
一位真正的绅士
Ah
啊
Yoga
瑜伽
Game over
游戏结束
In reverse
在相反的情况下
Um
嗯
Look
看
Thank you
谢谢
Oh no
哦不
Nothing
没有什么
Sorry
对不起的
Thanks god
感谢上帝
And style
以及风格
I am my mistake
我是我的错
What's going on
出什么事了
Are you on?
你上节目了吗？
What are you saying
你在说什么
Good night
晚安
I'm sorry, I'm talking about
抱歉，我说的是
Would you mind us?
你介意我们吗？
Go
去
I'm
我是
Who
谁
To set you Free
给你自由
Oh
哦
Don't get it
你不明白吗？
And uh
嗯
No
不
Then
然后
Possible
有可能
On
论
That was
你说的是
Let's do this
我们开始吧
Wonderful
好极了
Thank you
谢谢
Oh
哦
And uh
嗯
Um
She
她
What
什么
No
不
Son of
儿子
I'm attention please
我注意了，求你了
Get it done
把它做完
Straight up
一直往上走
Of course
当然
Okay so that's it
好吧，就这样
I can't be with them
我不能和他们在一起
Three
三
Here, you know, waiting for me choose
在这里，你知道，等着我选择
Are we together
我们在一起吗
Morning
早晨
And over again until I fell in love with you
一次又一次直到我爱上了你
What do you want
你想要什么
Relax
放松
And this is really interesting
很有意思的是
It's just
只是
What makes you
是什么让你
Do you have a chance to do something? Other people only dream of
你有机会做点什么吗？ 别人只会梦到
Who
谁
Uh
休斯敦大学
Thank
感谢
Oh
哦
Think again
再想想
Her face
她的脸
Yes
是的
Um
嗯
What's wrong
怎么了
You should go to hell
你应该下地狱
No
不
Don't
不要
Okay
可以
Well done
干得好
And so on
等等
Let's go to school once and for all
我们一劳永逸地去上学吧
Giants. Take me and my baby
巨人。带上我和我的孩子
My birthday last year
我去年的生日
Because it can wait
因为它可以等待
Yes
是的
For
为了
It's
它是
Mhm
MHM
It's nice
很好啊
Just tell me one thing
告诉我一件事
Are you pregnant
你怀孕了吗
Please morning
早上好
I know it's complicated
我知道这很复杂
What is this
这是什么？
Hello
你好
You know what
你知道吗
Good morning. Hundreds, two, and style
早上好。上百个，两个，还有风格
School is
学校是
The future is coming this summer
今年夏天，我们的未来将会到来
Thanks
谢谢
Take a chance on a minute
再给你一分钟的机会
So we're terrible. Tragedy continues to unfold. Details are still coming in, but so far we can confirm a nurse and police officer
所以我们很糟糕。悲剧还在继续。细节还在，但到目前为止我们可以确认一名护士和一名警官
Thank you
谢谢
And uh
嗯
Where are you going
你要去哪里
Noise
噪声
Oh
哦
Interesting
有意思
It's
它是
Uh
休斯敦大学
Um
嗯
Sure
当然
Can someone tell me
有人能告诉我
Take me in
带我进去
I said
我说
Amen
阿门
I'm
我是
Good
好
Trust me
相信我
Get involved with the guys
参与到那些人当中去
Something strange
一些奇怪的东西
Stop me back
把我挡在后面
Industry
工业
Um
嗯
Can you
你能
I'm tom and certain cleaning on making. So sorry, I explain price do you have
我是汤姆，正在做清洁工作。很抱歉，我解释价格你有
The conservatives his name?
保守派的名字？
Shows fine
很好啊
Eat
Bye
拜伊
Oh
哦
Fuck
操
Good morning
早上好
Are you OK
你还好吧
Do you want to do what's wrong
你想做什么不对的事吗
How much
多少钱
Thanks
谢谢
Happy birthday me more time
生日快乐，我有更多的时间
Apple
苹果
English so
英语，所以
And I can come up the morning
明天早上我就可以上来了
Are you kidding
你开玩笑吧
Can I have a totally different standing past actions
我能有一个完全不同的立场过去的行动
Hello, may I help you?
你好，有什么事吗？
That's correct. Answer it enters missing a person
是的，没错。回答它说少了一个人
Really
真的？
Okay
可以
Come on
快点
Happy birthday
生日快乐
And uh
嗯
Morning
早晨
Really
真的？
Morning
早晨
I noticed publicly condition
我注意到了公开的情况
Thank you
谢谢
I have something
我有东西
Good morning
早上好
Number
数
Iran
伊朗
And uh
嗯
Oh no
哦不
Really
真的？
Student
学生
Fuck
操
Office word
办公室用语
Baby
婴儿
Okay it's seven
好吧，现在是7点
I missed that day. I did not
我错过了那一天。我没有
Do you understand
你知道吗
I love meetings last
我喜欢最后一次见面
Nice
尼斯
I was with you back
我和你在一起
A minute
一分钟
English
英语
Sorry yes
抱歉，是的
So you're obligated to help them
所以你有义务帮助他们
As soon
很快
Right
对吗？
Noise
噪声
So on
等等
Oh my sister's
噢，我妹妹
Let's see
我来看看
Five
五
He didn't get angry
他没有生气
Mhm
MHM
Let me break the dean's office practice
我来打破院长办公室的规矩
Back
背部
And when she came from and we well
当她从我们家回来的时候
Please sit down
请坐
How do you do that?
你怎么做到的？
So
所以
I don't
我不
Yeah so
是这样
Okay
可以
Uh
休斯敦大学
Thank you
谢谢
What the ***
怎么了****
Thank you
谢谢
Oh
哦
Oh no
哦不
I don't know
我不知道
I'm trying to
我在试着
What are you working
你在做什么
Simple
简单的
Thank you
谢谢
And uh
嗯
Noise
噪声
Okay
可以
How are you?
你好吗？
Open
正常开放
Please
拜托
Noise
噪声
Let's go into them. Things happen
我们进去看看。世事难料
Risky time
危险的时刻
What comes next
接下来会发生什么
Are you
你是吗
Training
培训
Thank you
谢谢
One day away
一天后
Sorry
对不起的
Let's go
我们走吧
First
弗斯特
Are you
你是吗
Right
Noise
Thank you
谢谢
Say so easily
你说的太容易了
Thank you
谢谢
Good job
干得好
Problem
问题
Sorry sir
抱歉，先生
She
她
You know
你知道吗
Good morning person
早上好，各位
So
所以
Oh no
哦不
Listen carefully
仔细听好了
Would you like to dance?
你想跳舞吗？
It's nine thirty
已经九点半了
Of course
当然
Good
好
And uh
嗯
To go
外带
Excuse me
不好意思
So
所以
Noise
噪声
I'm so sorry
我很抱歉
OK
好啊
We need water
我们需要水
Are you OK
你还好吧
Am
氨
Smoking is
吸烟是
Uh
休斯敦大学
And uh
嗯
Noise
噪声
Yeah
是啊
For
为了
All
所有
Thank you
谢谢
Oh
哦
Thank you
谢谢
Woman
女人